(Sheldon:)So, what are we making today?
(Howard:)A small payload support structure for
a European science experimental package...
(Howard:)- ...that's going up on the next space shuttle.
- Really? How does it work?
(Howard:)It will be attached to the payload bay...
(Howard:)...and the sensor apparatus will rest on it.
Aha.
(Sheldon:)So it's a shelf.
(Howard:)No, you don't understand.
(Howard:)During acceleration, it needs
to stay perfectly level and provide...
(Howard:)Yeah, okay, it's a shelf.
(Sheldon:)I notice you're using titanium.
(Sheldon:)Did you give any consideration
to carbon nanotubes?
(Sheldon:)They're lighter, cheaper
and have twice the tensile strength.
(Howard:)Sheldon, there's a diploma in my office
that says I have a master's in engineering.
(Sheldon:)And you also have a note from your mother
that says, "I love you, Bubula."
(Sheldon:)But neither of those is a cogent argument
for titanium over nanotubes.
(Sheldon:)- Sheldon.
- Yes?
(Leonard:)Go away.
(Sheldon:)Did Leonard tell you to say that?